JUAN GARZÓN Web developer

PERSONAL INFORMATION

LOCALIZACIÓN

Cali, Colombia

TELÉFONO

+57 314 619 98 58

EMAIL

juandavidgr1002@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

Github

<u>Portafolio</u>

SKILLS

Javascript

React

Node

Express

Typescript

PostgreSQL

Sequelize

Redux

Mongodb

Graphal

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Web developer with over 700 hours of theoretical-practical academic experience in front-end and back-end technologies, including Javascript, React and Node. I participated in an academic group project where I learned to work effectively as a team and to solve problems effectively. I focus on providing scalable and user-friendly solutions, and look for opportunities to apply my skills in web application development and contribute to the company's growth.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer (Academic), Henry - Trainning contract

Remote

Dec 2022 - Ian 2023

- Participation in the design and development of a complete application on Animes as part of an agile development team of 4 developers.
- Responsible for the design of the application using Figma and the development of features such as registration, detail, filtering, user panel and subscription by plan.
- Work with the team to ensure proper integration and a smooth user experience.
- Improve desktop application performance by 36%, reducing charging time from 20s to 13s on 3g slow network.
- Collaborate on error and load management in the detail and home sections.
- Learn and implement new technologies such as Typescript, payment gateway with Paypal API, password encryption with bcrypt and third-party login with AuthO.

Full Stack Web Developer (Academic), Henry - Contrato de formación

Remote

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

- Development of a complete application on Pokemon using JavaScript, React, Node, Express, Sequelize, CSS, HTML, Redux. Responsive design...
- Learning and implementing good practices as a responsive design to improve user experience..

Tailwind

HTML5 y CSS3

Critical thinking

Autonomy

Effective communication

Commitment

HOBBIES

Learn and research new things about web development and design (UX, UI) . Also read, football and anime.

LANGUAGES

English B2 (Advanced Intermediate)

 Pro activity in the improvement of the application adding new functionalities that give value to the product. Planning tasks and meeting objectives.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer at Henry bootcamp

Remote

Jun 2022 - Feb 2023

More than 700 hours of theoretical-practical academic experience using both front-end and back-end technologies.

Business management (6 semester completed) at Universidad del Valle

Cali, Valle del Cauca, Colombia

Aug 2018

Unfinished formation.

PROJECTS

Soflink - Project management app (https://soflink.vercel.app/)

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

Collaborative (in real time) application for project management. Organize, add, assign and eliminate project tasks.

Techs: Typescript, React, Node, Express, Mongodb, Prisma, Graphql, Apollo, Websocket, HTML, TailwindCSS, AuthO.

Zero Two - Anime page (https://zerotwo-deploy.vercel.app/)

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

Web application that uses manipulates and manages Animes data brought from an external api (KitsuAPI). The application allows the user to view lists of anime, search and see the detail of the anime as its episodes. The user can interact by creating an account through either Google, which allows you to create lists and add favorites, as well as comment and manage your profile data or as your subscriptions.

Technologies used: Typescript, Javascript, React, Node, Express, Sequelize, Redux, HTML, CSS, AuthO, Paypal Developer API, Kitsu API.